Guide to the R.R. Donnelley & Sons Company Archive 1844-2005
University of Chicago Library
- Series XIII: Corporate Management
  - Subseries 3: Executive Speeches
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," William Blair and Company, June 27, 1991 (Box 730, Folder 22)
    - Carl K. Doty, "Paper and Print: An Enduring Partnership," Beloit/Measurex Papermaking Summit, July 9, 1991 (Box 730, Folder 23)
    - John R. Walter, "Dinner Remarks," Louis W. Cabot retirement, July 24, 1991 (Box 730, Folder 24)
    - John R. Walter, speech invitation (Box 730, Folder 25)
    - John R. Walter, employee roundtable, Dwight Division, August 9, 1991 (Box 730, Folder 26)
    - John R. Walter, employee roundtable, Harrisonburg Division, August 21, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 1)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "Printing's Digital Dilemma: Information Industrialists or Printing Farmers?" Tokyo Fair and Symposium of Print and Culture, September 20, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 2)
    - Carl K. Doty, "From Silver Halide to Laser Imaging: The Challenge to Traditional Printing," Print '91 Graphics Art Exposition, September 4, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 3)
    - W. Ed Tyler, "Imaging in the Global Environment," SPSE Symposium, September 11, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 4)
    - John R. Walter, "Opening Remarks," South Daytona plant dedication, September 16, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 5)
    - John A. Capstick, "Transnational Advertising: Recognizing a 'New World' When You See One," Spectrum '91, September 20, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 6)
    - John R. Walter, "Acceptance Remarks: Gravure Person of the Year," Gravure Association of America, October 15, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 7)
    - John R. Walter, employee roundtable, Reno Plant, October 28, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 8)
    - John R. Walter, "Panel Presentation," Direct Marketing Association Catalog Day Conference, November 3, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 9-10)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Ross Perot," Executives' Club of Chicago, November 22, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 11)
    - John R. Walter, speech, 80th Anniversary Dinner, Executives' Club of Chicago, December 4, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 12)
    - John R. Walter, Paine Webber Annual Conference on the Outlook for Media, December 10, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 13)
    - John R. Walter, speech, 1991 (Box 731, Folder 14)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Terry Savage," Executives' Club of Chicago, January 17, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 1)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," Annual Executive Meeting, Crain Communications, Inc., February 3, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 2)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," Leadership Greater Chicago," February 7, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 3)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of George Fisher," Executives' Club of Chicago, February 14, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 4)
    - Carl K. Doty, "Partnership: The New Strategy for Business," Presidents Conference, Printing Industries of America, February 26, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 5-6)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Margaret Thatcher and Richard Daley," Mid-America Committee, April 4, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 7)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of William H. Gates," Executives' Club of Chicago, April 7, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 8)
    - James R. Donnelley, "Provo Division Welcome," May 19, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 9)
    - John R. Walter, "Quick Scan Outline," Boston Security Analysts Society, Inc., May 28, 1991 (Box 732, Folder 10)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "Remarks," Institutional Investors Conference, William Blair and Company, June 23, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 11)
    - Rory J. Cowan, speech, Integral Strategy Conference, September 9, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 12)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," Documentation Services Group Sales Meeting, September 10, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 13)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," Crawfordsville Analysts Meeting, September 16, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 14)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "Remarks," Documentation Services Group, September 16, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 15)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of William Schreyer," Executives' Club of Chicago, September 18, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 16)
    - Bart Faber, speech, Seybold Conference, October 1992 (Box 732, Folder 17)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," Financial Services Sales Conference, October 19, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 18)
    - John R. Walter, speech, RR Donnelley and Time Warner, November 12, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 19)
    - John R. Walter, speech, New Member Reception, Executives' Club of Chicago, December 2, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 20)
    - John R. Walter, "Focusing on Today's RR Donnelley," Paine Webber Outlook for Media Conference, December 7, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 21-24)
    - Ken Coleman, "Facilitating a New Electronic Publishing Model," December 9, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 25)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Dick Ebersol," Executives' Club of Chicago, December 11, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 26)
    - Stock slides, 1992 (Box 732, Folder 27)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "Remarks," International Entertainment Media and Communication Conference, Smith Barney, January 13, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 1-5)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Terry Savage," Executives' Club of Chicago, January 15, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 6)
    - John R. Walter, after-dinner speech, Annual Meeting, RR Donnelley Florida Retirees' Club, January 29, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 7)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Richard J. Mahoney," Executives' Club of Chicago, February 12, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 8)
    - "Introduction of John R. Walter," University of Southern California Leadership Day, February 25, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 9-10)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "The Digital Elephant the Blindfolded Mahout: How Digital Imaging in Transforming the Printing Industry," Fifth World Print Conference, March 2, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 11-12)
    - Speech, annual meeting, March, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 13)
    - Rory J. Cowan, after-lunch speech, RR Donnelley Arizona Retirees' Club, March 16, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 14)
    - John A. Capstick, "Printing's Global Future," March 18, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 15)
    - Rhonda S. MacQueen, "Introduction of Martha Layne Collins," Chicago Historical Society, March 24, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 16)
    - John R. Walter, speech, annual meeting of shareholders, March 25, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 17)
    - John R. Walter, breakfast speech, Arthur Anderson, April 20, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 18)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of John H. Bryan," Executives' Club of Chicago, April 23, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 19)
    - John R. Walter, speech, New York City Media and Entertainment Analysts Group, May 4, 1993 (Box 733, Folder 20-22)
    - John R. Walter, speech, United Negro College Fund Campaign, Chicago Club, June 10, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 1)
    - John R. Walter, welcome, luncheon for Jaime Serra Puche, Executives' Club of Chicago, June 14, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 2)
    - John R. Walter, speech, New Members' Reception, Executives' Club of Chicago, June 17, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 3)
    - Speech, technology strategies, June 27, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 4)
    - Rory J. Cowan, speech, China Directories, July 1993 (Box 734, Folder 5)
    - Rory J. Cowan, Ron Weir, Barbara Schetter, and John Campanelli, presentation, Technology Strategies Show, July 22, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 6)
    - Rory J. Cowan, speeches, Technology Strategies Show and Vision 2000, July-September, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 7)
    - Speech, Fodor's 94, August 5, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 8)
    - John A. Capstick, introductory speech, Reader's Digest Association, August 5, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 9)
    - Rory J. Cowan, speech, Vision 2000, August 24, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 10)
    - Gary Oversmith, James R. Donnelley, Rory J. Cowan, and Jerry D. Butler, Newbern dedication speeches, September 9, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 11)
    - Frank R. Jarc, "Remarks," meeting and tour, New York Investment Community, September 28, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 12)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "Remarks," meeting and tour, New York Financial Analysts, September 29, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 13-16)
    - "Introduction of Helmut Schmidt," Executives' Club of Chicago, September 29, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 17)
    - Bart Faber, "Remarks," Seybold Conference, October, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 18)
    - Bart Faber and Ken Coleman, speeches to the Board of Directors, October, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 19)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Ross Perot," Executives' Club of Chicago, October 22, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 20)
    - John R. Walter, remarks, RR Donnelley Human Resources Conference, October 28, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 21)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," Security Analysts of San Francisco, November 9, 1993 (Box 734, Folder 22-23)
    - John R. Walter, "Communicating in a New Business Environment, with New Technology," alumni luncheon, Miami University, November 10, 1993 (Box 735, Folder 1)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," Magazine Publishers, November 15, 1993 (Box 735, Folder 2)
    - John R. Walter, "Tribute to John A. Capstick and Carl K. Doty," December 3, 1993 (Box 735, Folder 3)
    - Rory J. Cowan, speech, President's Club Luncheon, Financial Printing Services Group, December 4, 1993 (Box 735, Folder 4)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks" PaineWebber Media Conference, December 7, 1993 (Box 735, Folder 5-6)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Bert C. Roberts, Jr.," Executives' Club of Chicago, December 17, 1993 (Box 735, Folder 7)
    - Speechwriting templates and newsletter, 1993 (Box 735, Folder 8)
    - Speech invitations, 1993 (Box 735, Folder 9)
    - W. Ed Tyler, "Remarks," International Entertainment Media and Communications Conference, Smith Barney, January 10, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 10-11)
    - John R. Walter, message, Executives' Club of Chicago, January 17, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 12)
    - John R. Walter, "Technology and the Evolution of Print," Chicago Council Meeting, International Council on Management of Innovation and Technology, January 19, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 13)
    - John R. Walter, introduction, Economic Outlook, Executives' Club of Chicago, January 21, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 14)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," RR Donnelley Florida Retirees' Club, January 21, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 15-16)
    - Rory J. Cowan, speech, Conference Board, Strategic Management, February 2, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 17)
    - W. Ed Tyler, "Remarks on Orleans New Facility," March 11, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 18)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," United Way, March 15, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 19)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Jerry J. Jasinowski," Executives' Club of Chicago, March 18, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 20)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," annual meeting, March 24, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 21-22)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," Re-Engineering Committee, April 5, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 23)
    - James R. Donnelley, "Remarks," annual meeting, Arizona Chapter Lakeside Press Retired Employees' Club, April 5, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 24)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," University of Colorado-Boulder, April 12, 1994 (Box 735, Folder 25-27)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," annual meeting, Miami Friends of the Library, April 14, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 1)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Robert J. Eaton," Executives' Club of Chicago, April 15, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 2)
    - John R. Walter, speech, Re-Engineering Committee, April 15, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 3)
    - Rory J. Cowan, speech, Xerox Event, April 19, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 4-5)
    - Jonathan P. Ward, "Remarks," Toronto Society of Financial Analysts, May 5, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 6)
    - John R. Walter, speech, American Society of Corporate Executives, May 5, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 7)
    - John R. Walter, speech, Times-Mirror Magazines Conservation Council, May 6, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 8)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "Remarks," Boston Security Analysts Society, Inc., May 9, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 9)
    - W. Ed Tyler, "Remarks," Houston Society of Financial Analysts, May 11, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 10)
    - Ronald G. Eidell, "Remarks," Europe Analysts, May 16-20, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 11)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of the Honorable Richard M. Daley," Executives' Club of Chicago, May 20, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 12)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "Digital Printing and Reengineering: Made for Each Other," keynote address, On-Demand Printing and Publishing Conference, May 24, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 13-14)
    - "What They're Saying: Recent Speeches from RR Donnelley senior management," May 25, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 15)
    - John R. Walter, "Looking Opportunity in the Eye," Comprint International, May 29, 1994 (Box 736, Folder 16-19)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "Remarks," Conference Board, June 15, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 1)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "Digital Technology: Catalyst for Reengineering," PrintQuality '94, Rochester Institute of Technology, June 20, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 2-3)
    - Frank R. Jarc, "Remarks," Annual Campaign Victory Celebration, YMCA of Metropolitan Chicago, June 2, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 4)
    - Rory J. Cowan and Frank R. Jarc, "Remarks," Investment Conference, William Blair and Company, June 30, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 5-7)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "Redesigning the Book Printing Industry: A Digital Journey," July 26, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 8)
    - Frank R. Jarc, Jonathan P. Ward and Ronald G. Eidell, speeches, RR Donnelley Financial Meeting and Tour, South Daytona, Florida, September 1994 (Box 737, Folder 9)
    - Rory J. Cowan, "Donnelley Scalable Publishing Architecture: Catalyst for Dynamic-Brand Publishing," Seybold San Francisco Conference, September 13, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 10-11)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Richard L. Thomas," Executives' Club of Chicago, September 16, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 12)
    - John R. Walter, speech, Korn Ferry North American Executive Committee, September 16, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 13)
    - Jonathan P. Ward, "Electronic Crossroads and the Impact on our Industry," Spectrum '94, September 18, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 14-15)
    - John R. Walter, speech, Robert A. Hanson retirement dinner, September 21, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 16)
    - "Environmental Scan," presentation to the Board of Directors, September 22, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 17)
    - John R. Walter, "Paul Risser's Miami Initiative on Undergraduate Education for the Next Century," September 26, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 18)
    - James R. Donnelley, speech, grand opening of DPA Plant, Krakow, Poland, September 30, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 19)
    - John R. Walter, "Succeeding in Emerging Markets," American Society of Corporate Executives, October 1, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 20)
    - John R. Walter, "RR Donnelley and Safety: A Proud History," Safety Coordinators' Conference, October 12, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 21)
    - John R. Walter, "Leadership for Our Future: Goals 2000," Leadership Conference, October 19-21, 1994 (Box 737, Folder 22-23)
    - John R. Walter, eulogy for Herb Engel, October 24, 1994 (Box 738, Folder 1)
    - John R. Walter, speech, Patron's Breakfast, Harvard Business School Club of Chicago, November 20, 1994 (Box 738, Folder 2)
    - John R. Walter, speech, Jerry D. Butler retirement, November 21, 1994 (Box 738, Folder 3)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks," PaineWebber Media Week, December 8, 1994 (Box 738, Folder 4-5)
    - John R. Walter, "Remarks on Three Retirements," December 9, 1994 (Box 738, Folder 6)
    - "What They're Saying: Speeches from RR Donnelley's senior management," December 9, 1994 (Box 738, Folder 7)
    - John R. Walter, "Introduction of Michael R. Quinlan," Executives' Club of Chicago, December 16, 1994 (Box 738, Folder 8)
    - "What They're Saying: Speeches from RR Donnelley's senior management," December 19, 1994 Volume 1, Number 3; drafts of publication, 1994 (Box 738, Folder 9)
    - John R. Walter, "Crystal Ball for the '90s," American Society of Corporate Executives, March 10-12, 1995 (Box 738, Folder 10)
    - "What They're Saying," April 10, 1995 (Box 738, Folder 11)
    - John R. Walter, "Integrating New Technologies: It's a Matter of Perspective," January, 1996 (Box 738, Folder 12)
    - Jonathan P. Ward, "From Technology to Profitability: The Best is Yet to Come," Canadian Imperial Bank of Commerce Oppenheimer Publishing and Media/Information Services Conference, 1998 (Box 738, Folder 13)
    - Jonathan P. Ward, "Acting Big," speech to the Board of Directors, January 28, 1999 (Box 738, Folder 14)
    - Jonathan P. Ward, "Growth in the 21st Century: Preparation Meeting Opportunity!" New England Mail Order Association, March 26, 1999 (Box 738, Folder 15)
    - Jonathan P. Ward, speech, Canadian Imperial Bank of Commerce World Markets Conference, June 9, 1999 (Box 738, Folder 16)
    - Jonathan P. Ward, and William L. Davis, "A Strategy for Transformation," February 3, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 17)
    - William L. Davis, "Speech #1: Donnelley Reality," Leadership Conference, March 2, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 18-19)
    - William L. Davis, "Speech #2: Strategy and Organizational Structure," Leadership Conference, March 2, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 20)
    - Jonathan P. Ward, "Business Fundamentals," Leadership Conference, March 2, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 21)
    - Mike Allen, "Strategy 1: Transform Our Core Printing Businesses," Leadership Conference, March 3, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 22)
    - Joe Lawler, "Strategy 2: Speed Growth in High-Value Businesses," Leadership Conference, March 3, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 23)
    - Mike Winkel, "Strategy 3: Extend Logically into Complementary Businesses," Leadership Conference, March 3, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 24)
    - Jonathan P. Ward, "The Role of Leadership," Leadership Conference, March 3, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 25)
    - William L. Davis, "Speech #3: What Will Be Different," Leadership Conference, March 2-3, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 26)
    - Paul Masterson, transitional speeches, Leadership Conference, March 2-3, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 27)
    - William L. Davis and Jonathan P. Ward, question and answer sessions, Leadership Conference, March 23, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 28)
    - Planning materials, Leadership Conference, March 2-3, 2000 (Box 738, Folder 29)
  - Subseries 4: Organization Charts and Manuals
    - Officers and Executives, Printed Photographs, 1927 (Box 739, Folder 1)
    - Management Sequence, 1949-1978, Organizational manuals, 1949-1985 (Box 739, Folder 2)
    - Organizational manuals, 1949-1985 (Box 740)
    - Executive Officers and Staff Divisions, 1950 (Box 740, Folder 1)
    - Organizational manual, 1950 (Box 740, Folder 2)
    - Policy on nepotism, circa 1950 (Box 740, Folder 3)
    - Organizational Charts by Division with Photographs, manager/supervisor, circa 1950s (Box 740, Folder 4)
    - Administrative organizational charts, 1950-1991 (Box 740, Folder 5)
    - Policy book, 1952-1964 (Box 741)
    - Elected corporate officials and appointed Directors of the Divisions, 1954-1959 (Box 741, Folder 1)
    - Directors, officers and management listings from annual reports, 1956 (Box 741, Folder 2)
    - RR Donnelley by-laws, 1957 (Box 741, Folder 3)
    - "Organizational Adjustments to Meet our Growth," Charles C. Haffner, 1959 (Box 741, Folder 4)
    - Organizational documents, Organizational materials from Jim Bickers to John R. Walters, 1959-1974 Corporate policies manual, 1961-1967 "Developing an Organization Blueprint for Remainder of the Decade," 1984-1985, reports by Booz Allen and Hamilton Career Advancement Roster for Employees (CARE), 1972-1989 (Box 741, Folder 5-6)
    - Board of Directors listing, February 1985 (Box 741, Folder 7)
    - Corporate space study by Griswold Heckel and Kelly Associates, Inc., May 27, 1988, Organization charts, October 26, 1988 (Box 741, Folder 8)
    - President's Management council, 1988-1989 (Box 741, Folder 9)
    - Organization charts by group, 1989-1991 (Box 741, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors' Manual, professional members, 1991 (Box 741, Folder 11)
    - Humorous management chart, circa 1990s, Organization manual, 1991 "Human Resource Initiatives: Management Committee Meeting," March 25, 1994 (Box 741, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 5: Lakeside Trust
    - Charles C. Haffner, Lakeside Trust documents, 1935-1956 (Box 742, Folder 1-3)
    - Contracts, 1910-1951 (Box 742, Folder 4-19)
    - Copyrights, patents, and trademarks, 1926-1947 (Box 743, Folder 1-4)
    - Financial documents, 1925-1953 (Box 743, Folder 5-10)
    - Financial documents, audit documents and Northern Trust Receipts, 1956 (Box 743, Folder 11)
    - Financial documents, balance statements, 1952-1955 (Box 743, Folder 12)
    - Financial documents, depreciation records, 1931-1953 (Box 743, Folder 13)
    - Financial records, Richard R. Donnelley estate documents, 1950- 1951 (Box 743, Folder 14)
    - Financial records, RR Donnelley Michigan Company, 1947-1949 (Box 743, Folder 15-16)
    - Financing, Harrison Ripley and Company, 1954-1959 (Box 743, Folder 17-19)
    - Insurance, Commercial Union Assurance Company Limited, 1937- 1941 (Box 743, Folder 20)
    - Lloyd's Insurance, buildings, jewelry and art insurance, 1936-1945 (Box 743, Folder 21)
    - Mutual Life Insurance of New York; employee insurance, 1957 (Box 744, Folder 1)
    - Labor documents, 1921-1970 (Box 744, Folder 2)
    - Lease, Cowles Management, Incorporated, 1951-1952 (Box 744, Folder 3)
    - Lease, Lakeside Trust Trustees and RR Donnelley and Sons, November 1, 1952 (Box 744, Folder 4)
    - Lease, Radio Corporation of America Interchemical Color Correction device, 1951-1952 (Box 744, Folder 5)
    - Lease, RR Donnelley and Chicago-area warehouses, 1952-1957 (Box 744, Folder 6)
    - Liquidation documents, 1952-1956 (Box 744, Folder 7-9)
    - Loans, McCarthy Typesetting Company, 1920-1934 (Box 744, Folder 10)
    - Loans, Nathan Blackman, 1929-1930 (Box 744, Folder 11)
    - Loans, stocks from loans, 1917-1936 (Box 744, Folder 12)
    - Ordinances and permits, 1953-1954 (Box 744, Folder 13)
    - Receipts, 1920-1932 (Box 744, Folder 14)
    - Stock documents and company assessments, RR Donnelley, 1932- 1942 (Box 744, Folder 15)
    - Stock documents, RR Donnelley, 1939-1956 (Box 744, Folder 16-18)
    - Stock documents, RR Donnelley proxy agreement, 1952 (Box 744, Folder 19)
    - Stock documents, RR Donnelley SEC registration, 1956 (Box 744, Folder 20-21)
    - Stock documents, RR Donnelley stock prospectus, 1956 (Box 744, Folder 22)
    - Stock documents, stock receipts and certificates, RR Donnelley, 1946-1947 (Box 744, Folder 23)
    - Tax documents, RR Donnelley, 1891-1952 (Box 744, Folder 24-25)
    - Tax documents, RR Donnelley Illinois tax registration forms, 1936- 1955 (Box 744, Folder 26)
  - Subseries 6: Contribution Books
    - 1973-1985 (Box 745, Folder 1-18)
    - 1986-1989 (Box 746, Folder 1-12)
  - Subseries 7: Forecasting and Planning
    - Chicago Division, ten-year forecast for equipment, manning and activity, 1958 (Box 746, Folder 13)
    - Corporate Project Schedule, forward planning file, 1958 (Box 746, Folder 14)
    - Ten-year forecast, 1958 (Box 746, Folder 15-18)
    - Ten-year forecast, 1959 (Box 746, Folder 19)
    - Ten-year forecast, 1960 (Box 746, Folder 20)
    - Sales forecasts, 1964-1966 (Box 746, Folder 21)
    - Sales forecast, 1966 (Box 746, Folder 22)
    - Production forecast, 1966 (Box 746, Folder 23)
    - Long-range planning development, 1970-1971 (Box 746, Folder 24)
    - Long-range profit plans, 1972 (Box 746, Folder 25-26)
    - Long-range profit plans, 1973 (Box 746, Folder 27)
    - Equipment sales planning, 1974 (Box 747, Folder 1)
    - Digital Group, five-year strategic plan, 1982 (Box 747, Folder 2-3)
    - Calumet Center, five-year manufacturing plan, 1983 (Box 747, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Graphics, Central Division, five-year manufacturing plan, 1983 (Box 747, Folder 5)
    - Five-year strategic plans, 1983 (Box 747, Folder 6)
    - Eastern Financial Printing Division, five-year strategic plan, 1983 (Box 747, Folder 7)
    - Strategic plan presentations to the Board of Directors, 1983 (Box 747, Folder 8-10)
    - Eastern Financial Printing Division, strategic plan, 1984 (Box 747, Folder 11)